http://www.callawaygolf.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-CG4-Site/en_US/CustomerService-Show?fid=legal&cid=legal-privacy-policy&utm_medium=cg_site_links&utm_source=cgpo&utm_content=footer_links&utm_campaign=privacy_policy

on all orders.
Added to Cart!
Privacy Policy
Our Privacy Policy has been updated and has an Effective Date of January 1, 2020
This Callaway Golf Privacy Policy applies to the websites, mobile applications and other interactive features and online services, owned or operated by Callaway Golf Company or one of its subsidiary or affiliated companies (collectively, "Callaway") that post a link to or include this Privacy Policy (collectively, the "Sites"). This Privacy Policy describes our information and privacy practices with regard to the Sites and information we collect offline, which we may combine with online data.
Please take a moment to review this Privacy Policy.  Please also review the Terms and Conditions, which governs your use of the Sites. Please note that certain features or services discussed in this Privacy Policy may not be offered on the Sites at any particular time. By using these Sites, you agree to the collection, disclosure, and use of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy and the applicable Terms and Conditions, do not access or use the services or provide personal information to us.
Summary
This summary provides an overview of some important information regarding our collection, use, and sharing of information.  PLEASE REVIEW OUR FULL PRIVACY POLICY BEFORE USING OUR SITES.
We may collect personal information from you, which we primarily use in connection with your relationship with Callaway, your use of the Sites, processing your transactions, and for sending you information from us or on behalf of certain third parties.  We also automatically collect information through your use of the Sites, which may include information about your location.  We may also collect information about you from third parties.  Please review the "Information We May Collect Through the Sites And How We Collect It" and "How We May Use the Information Collected" sections of this Privacy Policy for a full description of the information we collect and how we use that information. Remember that if you participate in community forums and similar features on the Site, your information may be public.
We may share your information with our subsidiaries and affiliates, third party service providers, other third parties for a variety of business purposes, including direct marketing purposes. For more details, please review the section below titled "Sharing Information with Third Parties".
Callaway works with network advertisers, ad agencies, analytics providers, and similar vendors who may set and access their own tracking technologies (such as cookies and web beacons) and they may otherwise collect or have access to information about you and your interactions with us, and may use that information to serve you targeted ads on our Sites and elsewhere online. For more information, including your opt-out choices, please review our Ad and Cookie Policy.
Table Of Contents
Information We May Collect Through The Sites And How We Collect It
How We May Use The Information Collected
Sharing Information With Third Parties
Online Advertising And Analytics Providers
Our "Do Not Track” Policy
Changing Your Preferences And Accessing, Updating, Or Deleting Your Personal Information
These Sites Are Not Intended For Children
Data Security And Retention
Jurisdiction And Cross-Border Transfer
Third Party Content, Links To Other Sites, And Callaway Content Found Outside Of The Sites
Notice To California Residents
Notice To Nevada Residents
Contact Us
Changes To Privacy Policy
Information We May Collect Through The Sites And How We Collect It
We collect information from you directly, automatically when you visit the Sites, and sometimes from third parties. Some of this information may be considered "personal information" under various applicable laws.  We consider information that identifies you as a specific, identified individual to be personal information (such as your name, phone number, email address), and we treat additional information, including IP addresses and cookie identifiers, as "personal information" where required by applicable law.  And, if we combine information we consider to be non-personal with personal information, we will treat that combined information as personal information under this Privacy Policy.  Note that we may de-identify personal information so that it is non-personal, such as by aggregating it or converting it to a code, sometimes using a function commonly known as a "hash". We will treat de-identified information as non-personal to the fullest extent allowed by applicable law.
Information You Provide to the Sites
Callaway may ask you to provide information through or to the Sites when you interact with us, including contact information (such as your name, phone number, street address, and email address) and other information about you, such as demographic information (ZIP code, gender, income, and day and month of birth (for example), and information about your interests and preferences (such as information about your lifestyle or your golf game and your buying preferences). Under certain limited circumstances, for example if you are involved in a promotion, contest, or sweepstakes, we may also collect your Social Security Number (SSN), tax ID, passport number, and TSA pre-check or global entry number. You may provide personal information, demographic data and other information through various forms and features on the Sites.
In addition, some services on the Sites allow you to make purchases online, and therefore require that you supply us with information associated with your credit card information or other accepted form of payment as well as security information like your mother's maiden name.
Information You Provided Through Market Research Surveys
We may, from time to time, invite you to participate in market research surveys. The types of information that we collect from you may vary based on the objective of the survey or research activity, but may include your email address and social media handle and your responses to survey questions or forms. Any information you provide by participating in our market research focus groups is entirely voluntary and you have no obligation to provide any personal information or to respond any questions or portion of the research activity.
Callaway Community Forums, User Content, and Private Messenger
The Sites may provide you the opportunity to register and participate in posting content publicly in forums, through interactive features and through other communication functionality ("Callaway Community"). Those forums may ask you to create an account, may allow you to submit or post photographs, videos, questions, comments, suggestions, or other content (collectively "User Content"), and may have separate terms that govern your submission of data and use of the Community. If you create a profile, certain information will be made available to other users or the public, as disclosed on the Community page or within the Community terms. For example, you can organize certain submissions (such as images you upload) into public or private albums.
Note that anything you post to a Callaway Community Forum is public—others will have access to your User Content and may use it or share it with third parties. This also applies to information you choose to share publicly via your Personal Profile. Please review our Callaway Community Rules before posting.
If you submit User Content through a Community Forum, "Contact Us" feature or other means, and unless we otherwise state, the User Content may be used by Callaway for its business purposes and may be published online or offline (including, without limitation, on the Sites or any other format currently existing or later developed). In addition, and as further set forth in our Terms and Conditions we may use your User Content and any excerpt from your User Content in connection with our advertising, marketing, publicity, and promotional activities.
Callaway offers registered users a Private Messenger feature that allows users to connect with and send messages to each other.  Callaway may have access to those messages, but those messages will not be made publicly available and will not be directly used in our advertising campaigns. For more information, please see our Callaway Community Rules:
Information We Collect Automatically As You Access and Use the Sites
In addition to any personal information or other information you choose to submit to the Sites, we, and our third-party business partners (including, without limitation, any third-party advertisers and content or analytics providers), may use a variety of technologies that automatically or passively collect certain information whenever you visit or interact with the Sites ("Site Usage Information"). This Site Usage Information may include the website browser or operating system you are using, the URL or advertisement that referred you to our Sites, the search terms you entered into a search engine that led you to our Sites, all of the areas within our Sites that you visit, and the time of day, the next website you visit after leaving our Sites, among other information. We may use this Site Usage Information for a variety of purposes, including, without limitation, enhancing or otherwise improving the Sites. Site Usage Information is generally non-identifying, but if we associate it with you as a specific and identifiable person, we treat it as personal information. As you use the Sites, we will also track videos you watch and how you interact with the content.
In addition we automatically collect your IP address or other unique identifier ("Device Identifier") for your computer, mobile phone, or other device used to access the Sites. We may be able to collect or infer your approximate location through information we collect, such as an IP address. A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to your device used to access the Sites, and our servers identify your device by its Device Identifier.
Tracking Technologies
We use certain tracking technologies to collect Site Usage Information and Device Identifiers when you use our Sites, including cookies, web beacons, and embedded scripts. We use these technologies for a variety of reasons, such as to allow us to better understand how you use the Sites and interact with us. For a detailed description of the ways we and third parties collect information automatically and how it is used, please see our Ad and Cookie Policy.
Location Data
We may collect specific information about your location from your device. This may include your precise location. We may collect this using different types of technologies, including GPS and Wi-Fi. If you use our mobile app, we may also access your device’s location information in the background. You may be able to turn off the collection of location information through your device settings. However, please note that we may still be able to collect or infer your approximate location through other information we collect, such as IP address. In addition, some mobile service providers may also provide us or our third-party service providers with information regarding the physical location of the device used to access the Sites.
Fitbay Locations
If you visit one of our Fitbay locations, we may also collect information about you through CCTV cameras.  Our Fitbay CCTV cameras help us take measurements and monitor swings to help you choose the right club for you.
Send to a Friend Features and Information You Provide about Others
If you send a friend a communication through the Sites, the information you provide is used on a one-time basis to facilitate the communication and is not used for any other marketing purpose, unless we obtain consent from that person. If you otherwise disclose any personal information relating to other people to us, you represent that you have the authority to do so and permit us to use the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Information Third Parties Provide About You
We may receive information about you from third parties, including business partners and data providers. For example, if you are on another website and agree to receive information from Callaway, that website will forward your information to us so that we may contact you. We may also supplement the information we collect with outside records from third parties for various purposes, such as to provide you with information, services or products, to tailor our content and the offers we show you, or to enhance our products and services.
We may combine the information we receive from third parties with information we collect through the Sites. In those cases, we will apply this Privacy Policy to the combined information. The information collected and stored by the third party is subject solely to the third party’s privacy practices.
Social Media Interactions
The Sites may permit or facilitate interactions with an interactive third-party website or service ("Social Media"), such as enabling you to "like" or "share" content. If you choose to share content or otherwise post information from or via the Sites to Social Media, that information may be public and the third party may have access to information about you and your use of our Sites. You may also choose to participate on Social Media in a way that connects that third-party service with our Sites (such as posting to one of our pages on a Social Media site or signing into the Sites with your credentials from another website or service). Doing so may allow us to collect (or the third party to share) information about you.
We may also receive information about you if other users of Social Media give us access to their profiles and you are one of their connections or "friends". The information we collect is subject to this Privacy Policy. The information collected and stored by the third party remains subject to the third party’s privacy practices, including, without limitation, whether the third party continues to share information with us, the types of information shared, and your choices with regard to what is visible to others on that third-party website or service. The third party may allow you to remove the application or feature, in which case we will no longer collect information about you through the application or feature, but may retain the information previously collected.
How We May Use The Information Collected
Callaway may use information collected through the Sites:
To allow you to participate in the Sites and features we offer. We may use your information to provide you with services, and allow you to participate in features and activities we offer. This may include processing information you provide via your account registration with the Sites, including, verifying that your email address is active and valid.
We communicate with you and tailor content, ads, offers. We may use your information to personalize your experience and tailor content we display to you, such as advertising, recommendations, promotions, and offers we display to you, both on the Sites and elsewhere online. We may also communicate with you about our products and services (including marketing messages and transactional messages relating to your use of our Sites or changes to our policies), and may send you  special offers and promotions from us, our advertisers, and third-party partners using the contact information you provide.
In connection with your purchases and for customer service. We use information to fulfill transactions, process payments and orders, and send you confirmations and receipts.  We also use information to provide customer service, including in connection with any delivery, billing, or payment processing inquiries.
To operate and protect our Sites. We use information for internal business purposes such as to improve our Sites or our products and services and to comply with regulatory and legal obligations.  We also use information about our users to protect our Sites and our customers from errors, misuse of the Sites, fraud, or any criminal activity and detect and troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes, and enforce applicable agreements and policies for the Sites.
We may also use information for any other purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy, as disclosed at the time you provide your information, or otherwise with your consent.
Sharing Information With Third Parties
Callaway may share non-personal information, which may include information that has been de-identified, or a Callaway identification or transaction number, with third parties. In addition, Callaway may share this information we have collected about you as allowed by law and as disclosed at the time you provide your information or otherwise with your consent, as described in this Privacy Policy and in the following circumstances:
Third Parties for Their Marketing Purposes. We may share information with third parties who may use your information for their own direct marketing purposes. For example, these third parties may include our retail partners where you purchase Callaway products. These third parties may use the information for their own purposes, including their own marketing and advertising purposes. California residents please see below for additional information in "Notice to California Residents."
Callaway Family of Companies. Callaway includes several brands and companies, some of which operate as subsidiaries, affiliates or joint ventures.  When Callaway collects information on one of our Sites, it will be accessible across the Callaway family of brands and companies.  The information will be used for business, operational and marketing purposes. California residents, please see below for additional information in "Notice to California Residents".
When You Request That We Share Your Information. We may share information when you direct us to do so. For example, you may be presented with an opportunity to receive marketing offers from a third party or you may engage with a Social Media service or other third party application or feature, through which information about you is shared. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties. If you later decide that you no longer want to receive communications from a third party, you will need to contact that third party directly.
Third Parties Providing Services on Our Behalf.  We may share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf, such as website hosting, conducting website usage analysis, sending email or other communications, fulfilling orders, providing marketing assistance and data analysis, processing payments (including clearing and processing credit card payments), running promotions, or performing other services. We may provide access to your personal information to such service providers in order for them to perform these services. You can contact us if you want to learn more about how our service providers use your information.
Sweepstakes, Contests, Promotions.  We may offer sweepstakes, contests, or other promotions (any, a "Promotion"), that may require registration. By participating in a Promotion, you are agreeing to the provisions, conditions, or official rules that govern the Promotion, which may require specific requirements of you (including, without limitation, and except where prohibited by law, allowing the sponsor(s) of the Promotion to use your name, voice, likeness, or other indicia of persona in advertising or marketing materials). If you choose to enter a Promotion, personal information may be disclosed to third parties or the public in connection with the administration of such Promotion, including, without limitation, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, as required by law or permitted by the Promotion’s terms or official rules (such as on a winners list).
Administrative and Legal Reasons.  Callaway may transfer and disclose information to third parties to comply with a legal obligation, when we believe in good faith that the law requires it; at the request of government or investigatory authorities conducting an investigation; to verify or enforce our Terms and Conditions or other applicable Sites policies; or otherwise to protect our rights, property, safety, or security or that of other Sites visitors or the public, such as when we are investigating potential fraud. For example, we may share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may also use Device Identifiers to identify users, and may do so in cooperation with copyright owners, Internet service providers, wireless service providers, or law enforcement agencies, in our discretion.
Employment Applications. If you apply for a job with Callaway or any of our subsidiaries or affiliates, we or our service provider(s) may ask you to provide self-identifying information (such as veteran status, gender, and ethnicity) in conjunction with laws and regulations enforced by the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission and other federal, state and local regulatory agencies. Providing such self-identifying information is voluntary, but if you do provide such information, we and/or our service providers may submit that information to the appropriate government or regulatory agencies to fulfill reporting requirements and use that information to defend against employment-related complaints.
Please note that we may utilize a careers portal that is operated by a third party, in which case your use of the careers portal will be subject to the third party’s privacy practices as disclosed on the portal, and not to this policy.
Business Transfers.  In the event Callaway goes through a transition such as being sold, has all or a portion of its assets acquired or transferred, whether voluntary or involuntary (such as through bankruptcy), or merges or becomes affiliated with any other division, individual or entity (including, without limitation, during the course of any due diligence process), any customer information owned or under the control of Callaway will likely be one of the transferred assets. We reserve the right, as part of this type of transaction, to assign or otherwise transfer your information and other information we have collected from users of the Sites.  By providing your personal information, you agree that we may transfer such information to the acquiring entity without your further consent.  For example, if part of our business was sold we may give our customer list as part of that transaction. Where legally required, we will give you prior notice and if you have the legal right to do so, allow you to object.
Online Advertising and Analytics Providers
BELOW WE PROVIDE A BRIEF OVERVIEW OF OUR THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING AND ANALYTICS PRACTICES. FOR A FULL DESCRIPTION AND TO LEARN MORE ABOUT HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION FOR THESE PURPOSES, PLEASE READ OUR AD AND COOKIE POLICY.
We work with a variety of third party business partners, such as network advertisers, ad agencies, and other advertising partners to serve Callaway ads online and through our Sites. We and these third parties use information we have learned about you to target ads to you. We also use analytics providers to provide us with information regarding the use of Callaway Sites and the effectiveness of our advertisements. These third parties may set and access their own tracking technologies on your device (including cookies and web beacons) and they may otherwise collect or have access to information about you. We and our third party advertising and analytics providers may collect personal information over time when you visit the Sites or other online websites and services.
We use Google Analytics, which uses cookies and similar technologies to collect and analyze information about use of the Sites and report on activities and trends. This service may also collect information regarding the use of other websites, apps, and online services. You can learn about Google’s practices by going to google.com/policies/privacy/partners, and opt out of them by downloading the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, available at tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Some of these third party advertising and analytics providers are members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") or the Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA") Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. You may want to visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp, which provides information regarding targeted advertising and "opt-out" procedures of NAI members. You may also want to visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices/, which provides information regarding targeted advertising and offers an "opt-out" by participating companies in the DAA Self-Regulatory Program.  To learn more about interest-based advertisements from participating third parties in jurisdictions outside of the United States, please visit the Canadian DAA online choice page at http://youradchoices.ca/choices/ and the European DAA online choice page at http://youronlinechoices.eu/.
For mobile applications, you may be able to limit certain advertising practices using the settings on your phone, tablet, or other mobile device. Also, on most mobile devices, you can install the DAA’s AppChoices app to make choices about cross-app interest-based advertisements from participating third parties. You may review additional information on opting out of mobile devices at https://www.networkadvertising.org/mobile-choice/.
If you are a California resident, please see our "California Privacy Notice" regarding additional rights you have, including how to exercise your "Do Not Sell" right.
Please note that opting out through these mechanisms does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads while online.
Our "Do Not Track" Policy
Some browsers have "Do Not Track" features that allow you to tell a website not to track you. These features are not all uniform and there is no consensus as to what "Do Not Track" means in this context. Callaway uses commercially reasonable efforts to detect and process "Do Not Track" signals. To find out more about "Do Not Track", please visit www.allaboutdnt.com.
Changing Your Preferences and Accessing, Updating, or Deleting Your Personal Information
You may be able to change your preferences with regard to the communications you receive from us for one or more of our Sites by logging into the "My Account" or similar page for a Site. You may also contact us by clicking here to make a request to review your information and to request changes or deletion. Changing your preferences for one of our divisions or Sites may not change your preferences for all Callaway Sites. You may opt out of receiving marketing e-mails by following the opt-out instructions provided to you in those e-mails.
If you want to opt out of having your information shared with unaffiliated third parties for their own marketing purposes, please email us.
Please note that we reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to your account or use of the Sites (for example, order confirmations or responses to communications we receive from you) and these transactional account messages may be unaffected if you opt-out from marketing communications.
You can turn off the GPS locator on your device. You can also turn off push notifications in your device settings.
If Callaway offers and you choose to sign-up to communicate with us via text message, you may unsubscribe by replying "STOP."
You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of the information you submit to us, such as your contact information. You may update the information you have provided to us by logging into the "Account" setting or similar page for one of the Sites. Callaway will make good faith efforts to make requested changes in our then active databases as soon as reasonably practicable. Note, however, that information may persist internally for administrative purposes and that residual data may remain on backup media or for other reasons.
Other Privacy Rights. If you are a California resident, please see our "Notice to California Residents" for additional information about how to exercise your privacy rights. If you are a Nevada resident, please see our "Notice to Nevada Residents" for more information on additional rights you may have.
The Sites Are Not Intended For Children
The Sites are general audience and do not target users younger than the age of 18.  We do not knowingly collect personal information online from children younger than the age of eighteen (18).  If you are a parent or guardian and think we have information about your child, please contact us.
Data Security and Retention
Callaway uses commercially reasonable security measures designed to secure your personal information. However, no data transmission over the Internet, wireless transmission or electronic storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Callaway cannot guarantee that the Internet or your mobile device will be completely secure and cannot warrant or ensure the security of any information we collect. You use our Sites and provide us information at your own risk.
We store personal information for as long as necessary for the purposes for which it was collected or for which you subsequently authorize it and otherwise to carry out the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. We will also store personal information for as long as we are required to keep it because of legal obligations, professional accounting and audit standards, legal or insurance claims, or regulatory proceedings.
Jurisdiction and Cross-Border Transfer
These Sites are controlled and operated by Callaway from the United States and are not intended to subject Callaway to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country or territory other than that of the United States. Callaway makes no representation that this Privacy Policy or the practices described in it comply with the laws of any other jurisdiction. If you are located outside of the United States, any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. Visitors who use the Sites and reside outside the United States do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable.
Your personal information may be stored and processed in any country where we have facilities or in which we engage service providers, and, by using these Sites and giving us your information, you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside your country of residence, including, without limitation, the United States, which may have data protection rules that are different from those of your country and may not provide the same level of protections as the laws of your country.
Third Party Content, Links To Other Sites, and Callaway Content Found Outside Of The Sites
Certain content on the Sites may be hosted and served by third parties, and the Sites may contain links to third party websites that Callaway does not control. For example, our Sites may provide links to third party sites through which you can watch videos, purchase merchandise, products or services or which link to a product or service offered by a third party. The Sites may also contain certain third-party applications, such as email, web browser toolbars, wallpapers, or other downloads or software applications. These links and applications may include, for example, those that use a Callaway logo as part of a co-branding agreement. In addition, Callaway widgets or other Callaway content may be included, among other places, on web pages and websites that are not associated with Callaway and over which we have no control. These third parties may collect Site Usage Information through the use of their own cookies and web beacons, independently collect data or solicit personal information, and may have the ability to track your use of their sites and services. Callaway is not responsible for the privacy or other practices employed by any third party.
Notice To California Residents
1. CALIFORNIA PRIVACY NOTICE
This California Privacy Notice is effective as of January 1, 2020.
This notice supplements Callaway’s privacy policy and applies only to California residents.  This California Privacy Notice sets forth the disclosures and rights for California consumers regarding their personal information, as required by the California Consumer Privacy Act ("CCPA").  Terms used in this California Privacy Notice have the same meanings given in the CCPA and the regulations of the Attorney General implementing the CCPA, unless otherwise defined.
This notice provides information about the categories of information that we collect from California residents generally, the sources of the information, the purposes for which we use the information, and the categories of third parties to whom we disclose the information for business purposes and to whom we sell Personal Information as defined by CCPA (and information on how to opt-out).
INFORMATION CALLAWAY COLLECTS
Callaway collects information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or device ("Personal Information").
The following are the categories of Personal Information that we have collected from our users over the last 12 months (and examples of the types of information those include), the categories of sources from which that information was collected, the business or commercial purpose(s) for which the information was collected, the categories of third parties with whom we disclose the information for a business purpose, and the categories of third parties to whom this type of personal information is sold.
The Personal Information we collect about you will depend upon how you use our Sites or otherwise interact with us. Accordingly, we may not collect all of the below information about you. We may also collect and/or use additional types of information after providing notice to you before collection and obtaining your consent (to the extent such notice and consent is required by the CCPA).
Category of Personal Information
Collected
Categories of Sources from which the
Information was Collected
Business or Commercial Purpose(s) for which Information is Collected
Categories of Third Parties to whom
this type of Personal Information is Disclosed for a Business Purpose
Categories of Third Parties to Whom
this Type of Personal Information is Sold
Identifiers
This category includes
information such as name, contact information, and online or device
identifiers.
We
may collect this type of information from:
Consumers,
Cookies and Tracking Technologies,
Third Party Service Providers,
Third party social media companies,
Third party business partners,
Third party data resellers.
We
may use this type of information:
To allow you to participate in the Sites and
features we offer,
To communicate with you and tailor content,
ads, and offers,
in connection with your purchases and for
customer service,
to operate and protect our Sites
We may disclose this type of
information to:
Service Providers,
Third parties who deliver our
communications,
Third parties we partner with for contests, sweepstakes,
or promotions,
Third party advertising and analytics
companies,
Other third parties (including government
agencies) as required by law (such as pursuant to subpoenas or court orders).
Third party advertising business
partners may have access to this data, including to better serve you more
relevant and sometimes location based advertisements, and this may be
considered a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances.
Any categories of personal information described in
subdivision (e) of Section 1798.80
This category includes
name, address, and phone number, information about your employment or
education, and other categories of information
classified as "personal" under this California law.
We
may collect this type of information from:
Consumer,
Cookies and Tracking Technologies,
Third Party Service Providers,
Third party social media companies,
Third party business partners,
Third party data resellers.
We
may use this type of information:
To allow you to participate in the Sites and
features we offer,
To communicate with you and tailor content,
ads, offers,
In connection with your purchases and for
customer service,
To operate and protect our Sites
We may disclose this type of
information to:
Service Providers
Third parties who deliver our
communications,
Third parties we partner with for contests,
sweepstakes, or promotions,
Third party advertising and analytics
companies,
Other third parties (including government
agencies) as required by law (such as pursuant to subpoenas or court orders).
Third party advertising business
partners may have access to this data, including to better serve you more
relevant and sometimes location based advertisements, and this may be
considered a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances.
Characteristics of protected classifications under
California or federal law
This category includes
information such as age, sex (including gender), national origin,
citizenship, and marital status.
We
may collect this type of information from:
Consumers,
Job applicants,
We
may use this type of information for job applicants:
For background screening to assess
applications for employment;
For your benefits enrollment;
For compensation benchmarking;
For consumers,
we may use this type of information to perform market
research that allows Callaway to better understand its demographic market.
We may disclose this type of
information to:
Service Providers
Other third parties (including government or
regulatory agencies) as required by law.
We do not sell this information.
Commercial information
This category includes,
for example, payment information you provide for goods, services, customer service
records, and information about the products you have purchased.
We
may collect this type of information from:
Consumer,
Third
Party Service Providers,
Third party business partners.
We
may use this type of information:
To allow you to participate in the Sites and
features we offer,
in connection with your purchases and for
customer service,
to operate and protect our Sites.
We may disclose this type of
information to:
Service Providers
Third parties who deliver our communications,
Third parties we partner with for contests,
sweepstakes, or promotions,
Third party advertising and analytics
companies,
Other third parties (including government
agencies) as required by law (such as pursuant to subpoenas or court orders).
Third party advertising business
partners may have access to this data, including to better serve you more
relevant and sometimes location based advertisements, and this may be
considered a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances.
Biometric information
We
may collect this type of information from:
Consumers
We
may use this type of information:
To assist you in finding the right club.
To allow you to participate in the Sites and
features we offer.
We may disclose this type of information
to:
Service Providers
Other third parties (including government
agencies) as required by law (such as pursuant to subpoenas or court orders).
We
do not sell this information.
Internet or other electronic network activity information
This category includes
information about the web browser and operating system you are using, the
website or ad that referred you to our Sites, areas of the Sites that you
visited, and terms entered into a search engine that led you to the Sites.
We
may collect this type of information from:
Consumer,
Cookies and Tracking Technologies,
Third Party Service Providers,
Third party social media companies,
Third party business partners,
Third party data resellers.
We
may use this type of information:
To allow you to participate in the Sites and
features we offer,
to operate and protect our Sites
We may disclose this type of
information to:
Service Providers
Third party advertising and analytics
companies,
Other third parties (including government agencies)
as required by law (such as pursuant to subpoenas or court orders).
Third party advertising business
partners may have access to this data, including to better serve you more
relevant and sometimes location based advertisements, and this may be considered
a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances.
Geolocation data
This is the precise location (e.g., within 16 ft.) of the device you
are using.
We
may collect this type of information from:
Consumer,
Cookies and Tracking Technologies,
Third Party Service Providers.
We
may use this type of information:
To allow you to participate in the Sites and
features we offer,
To communicate with you and tailor content,
ads, offers,
to operate and protect our Sites
We may disclose this type of
information to:
Service Providers
Third party advertising and analytics
companies,
Other third parties (including government
agencies) as required by law (such as pursuant to subpoenas or court orders).
Third party advertising business
partners may have access to this data, including to better serve you more
relevant and sometimes location based advertisements, and this may be
considered a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances.
Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar
information
This category includes,
for example, images, video, or audio recordings.
We
may collect this type of information from:
Consumer
We
may use this type of information:
To assist you in finding the right club.
To allow you to participate in the Sites and
features we offer.
We may disclose this type of
information to:
Service Providers
Other third parties (including government
agencies) as required by law (such as pursuant to subpoenas or court orders).
We
do not sell this information.
Professional or employment-related information
This category includes job applications and current and/or past
employers.
We
may collect this type of information from applicants for employment
We
may use this type of information to assess applications for employment
We
may disclose this type of information
Service Providers
Other third parties (including government
agencies) as required by law (such as pursuant to subpoenas or court orders).
We
do not sell this information.
Inferences drawn from any of the information identified
above to create a profile about a consumer
These inferences may relate to your perceived interests, preferences,
characteristics, or behavior.
We
may collect this type of information from:
Consumer,
Cookies and Tracking Technologies,
Third Party Service Providers,
Third party social media companies,
Third party business partners,
Third party data resellers.
We
may use this type of information:
To allow you to participate in the Sites and
features we offer,
To tailor content, ads, offers,
to operate and protect our Sites.
We may disclose this type of
information to:
Service Providers,
Third parties we partner with for contests,
sweepstakes, or promotions,
Third party advertising and analytics
companies.
Third party advertising business
partners may have access to this data, including to better serve you more
relevant and sometimes location based advertisements, and this may be
considered a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances.
EXERCISING YOUR CALIFORNIA ACCESS, DELETION AND DO NOT SELL RIGHTS
California residents have the right to request that we disclose to you what Personal Information we collect, use, disclose, and sell, including the right to request that we provide to you the specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you in the prior 12 months ("Right to Know") and you have the right to ask us to delete the Personal Information we collect about you ("Right to Delete"), subject to exceptions set forth in the CCPA.
California residents also have the right to opt-out from the sale of their Personal Information. These rights are subject to some limitations, such as when we are retaining data to comply with our own legal obligations. You will not be required to create an account with us in order to submit a request. More information on each of these rights is below.
If you would like to authorize an agent to act on your behalf in submitting a request to know, request to delete, or request to opt-out of the sale of your Personal Information, you may do so by following this link. Please keep in mind that if we do not receive adequate proof that the agent is authorized to act on your behalf, we may deny the request.
Response Timing
When you request access to the Personal Information we have collected or deletion of your Personal Information, we will typically provide the requested information within 45 days, and we will notify you within that time period if we need additional time to process your request. When you opt-out from the sale of your Personal Information, we will honor your request as soon as feasibly possible, but no later than 15 days from the date we receive your request.
RIGHT TO KNOW
Making A Request
To request the specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you in the prior 12 months, please complete this form or call us toll-free at 1-833-681-0358.
We will provide the requested information free of charge up to two (2) times in a 12-month period, but please note that where we receive unfounded, excessive, or repetitive requests, we may elect to decline the request. We will not retain information we do not ordinarily retain in the course of our regular business practices.
Verifying Requests to Access
Please note that we will take steps to verify your identity in order to fulfill your request. We will first verify your email address is active and we will take steps to verify the information you provide to us. If you have an account with us, please have your account information available when you call or visit our portal to facilitate verification.
In order to verify your identity, we will request that you provide: your name, email address, and zip code.
In order to have us provide specific pieces of information, we will require a signed declaration under penalty of perjury that you are the consumer whose Personal Information is the subject of the request.
If we are unable to verify that the individual submitting the request is the same individual about whom we have collected information (or someone authorized by that individual to act on their behalf), we will not be able to provide the requested information.
RIGHT TO DELETE
The CCPA also provides a right to request that we delete personal information we have collected about you and for us to direct service providers to do the same, with certain exceptions as set forth in the CCPA.  Note that you may also delete certain Personal Information you have provided to us through your online account.
When processing a request to delete, we may erase some information and we may de-identify some information. When we de-identify information, we implement technical safeguards and business processes that prohibit re-identification, business processes to prevent inadvertent release of de-identified information, and will make no attempt to re-identify the information.
Making A Request
If you are a California resident and would like to request that we delete your information, please submit your request by completing the request form or calling us toll-free at 1-833-681-0358.
Verifying Requests to Delete
To ensure that we do not delete your personal information in response to a fraudulent request, once you submit the request, we will follow up to confirm that you want your information to be deleted.
In order to verify your identity, we will request that you provide: your name, email address, and zip code.
If we are unable to verify that the individual submitting the request is the same individual about whom we have collected information (or someone authorized by that individual to act on their behalf) we will not delete the information but we will process the request as a "Do Not Sell" request.
RIGHT TO OPT-OUT OF THE SALE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
The CCPA also provides a right to request to opt-out of the sale of your Personal Information. Callaway engages in online advertising practices that may potentially be considered "sales" under the CCPA. To opt-out of cookies set by 3rd parties that may be considered "sales" under the CCPA, click the Decline button within the notification bar at the bottom of the site. If you have already closed the notification bar, please close your browser and open a new session.
In addition, as we discuss above in our privacy policy, some of the companies we work with for analytics and advertising purposes are members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") or the Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA") Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising and you may want to visit the following webpages, which provide "opt-out" mechanisms for participating companies: http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp and http://www.aboutads.info/choices/.  You may opt-out from interest based advertising on your mobile device through your mobile device settings.
Users Younger than Age 16
Callaway does not knowingly sell Personal Information of minors younger than 16 years of age without affirmative authorization.
Right to Non-Discrimination for the Exercise of a Consumer’s Privacy Rights
California consumers have the right to not receive discriminatory treatment for exercising CCPA rights.  We will not discriminate against you for exercising your CCPA rights.
Contact for More Information
You can contact us for more information by writing to us at Callaway Golf, Attn: Law Department, 2180 Rutherford Road, Carlsbad, CA 92008 or calling us at 1-833-681-0358.
2. Other California Rights/YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, residents of the State of California who provide us personal information, as covered by California’s Civil Code Section 1798.83, have the right to request and obtain from us one time per calendar year information about the customer information we shared, if any, with third parties for their own direct marketing purposes during the preceding year.  If applicable, this information would include the categories of customer information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information for the immediately preceding calendar year.
If you are a California resident and wish to obtain this information from us, please send your request via email or write to us at the following mailing address: CA Privacy Rights, Callaway Golf, Attn: Law Department, 2180 Rutherford Road, Carlsbad, California 92008. You must put the statement "Your California Privacy Rights" in the subject field of your email or include it in your writing if you choose to write to us at the designated mailing address. You must include your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information.
Notice to Nevada Residents
Pursuant to Nevada law, you have the right to opt-out of the sale of certain covered personally identifiable information (PII) we have collected about you through our websites and online services. Please note that Callaway does not sell your covered information as those terms are defined under applicable Nevada law. However, you may still submit an opt-out request and we will honor that request as required by Nevada law if we were to engage in such a sale in the future. If you are a Nevada resident and would like to opt-out of future sales of your information, please call 1-833-681-0358.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Policy, please email us at webmaster@callawaygolf.com.
You can also write to us or call us at:
Callaway Golf
Attn: Law Department
2180 Rutherford Road
Carlsbad, CA 92008
Phone: 760-931-1771
Changes to Privacy Policy
To the extent allowed by applicable law, Callaway reserves the right to change or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and will notify you of material changes by posting the changed or modified Privacy Policy on our Sites. We may also provide notice to you in other ways, such as through contact information you have provided. Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy unless otherwise specified.  Your continued use of the Sites after the effective date of the revised Privacy Policy (or such other act as specified in the revised Privacy Policy) will constitute your consent to those changes to the fullest extent allowed by applicable law. However, Callaway will provide notice and obtain your consent (which may be opt-out consent or which may occur through your continued use of the Site) to the new policy if required. Note that you may need to consent to our new policies in order to continue to use our Sites and services.
© 2019 Callaway Golf Company
30-Day Money Back Guarantee
Not Satisfied? Return Your Product for a Refund.
Easy Payments
Make Easy Payments Over 3,6 or 12 Months
Free Shipping & Returns
*Free Ground Shipping on All Orders
No promo or coupon codes are required
Only valid with UPS Ground
Shipping discounts will automatically apply
Sorry, this free shipping offer is not valid in conjunction with GMC promo coupons or any type of Shopping Spree gift cards.
This offer excludes custom logo orders.
*Free 2-Day Shipping On Orders Over $200
Free 2-Day Shipping On Orders Over $200
No promo or coupon codes are required
Shipping discounts will automatically apply when you reach the $200 threshold and select UPS 2 Business Day shipping
Sorry, this free shipping offer is not valid in conjunction with GMC promo coupons or any type of Shopping Spree gift cards.
This offer excludes custom logo orders and shipping to Hawaii or Alaska.
Free Return Shipping
Callaway Golf wants you to be fully satisfied with every item you purchase. If you are not satisfied with the item you have purchased, you may return it within 30 days of shipment for a full refund of the product price.
If product is unused the refund will credit back to your original payment method.
If product has been used the refund will be in the form of a CallawayGolf.com Gift Card with no expiration date.
In either case a Return Merchandise Authorization(RMA) is required. To obtain a Return Merchandise Authorization (RMA) and your
FREE UPS Return Shipping Label, please contact a Sales and Customer Service Representative toll free at
1-877-723-5218 or
email us.
Still not a member of Callaway Rewards? Join & start earning points.
Join Today
*No coupon code required. In some instances, items will ship when they become available, not necessarily when the order is placed. Free shipping available only to addresses within the contiguous US.
Close
2-Year Warranty
Callaway Products are Backed for Two Years
Warranty Coverage: Except as otherwise stated on the product or packaging, Callaway Golf Company warrants its golf clubs, components, and other products purchased from an authorized Callaway Golf retailer or distributor to be free of defects in material and workmanship for two years. Callaway Golf will, without charge to the consumer, repair or replace any product or component or part thereof that is defective or becomes defective during normal use within two years after the date of purchase from an authorized Callaway Golf retailer or distributor. At its option, Callaway Golf may replace the product with a new or refurbished product. Callaway Golf does not warrant its products against damage caused by third parties. This warranty does not cover paint scratches, cosmetic blemishes or other normal wear and tear. Callaway Golf will fix such blemishes and scratches, however, for a fee. To obtain warranty service in the United States on a complete Callaway Golf product, return the product to a Callaway Golf authorized retailer or directly to Callaway Golf. In the case of a Callaway Golf component, you must obtain warranty service through an authorized Callaway Golf retailer of that component. Outside of the United States, all warranty service must be obtained from the distributor or subsidiary in the country in which the club was purchased. To determine the Callaway Golf authorized retailer, distributor or subsidiary nearest you, check our website at www.callawaygolf.com or contact Callaway Golf directly. In California call collect 760-931-1771; outside California call toll free 1-800-588-9836.
Disclaimer: This warranty is in lieu of all other express warranties. Callaway Golf disclaims all warranties for products that are purchased from sellers other than authorized retailers or distributors, including the warranty of merchantability or the warranty of fitness for a particular purpose. Callaway Golf also disclaims any implied warranty, including the warranty of merchantability or the warranty of fitness for a particular purpose, and assumes no responsibility for any special, incidental, or consequential damages as to all products and components. Callaway Golf further disclaims any implied or express warranty of, and assumes no responsibility for, defects in workmanship caused by third parties. This warranty gives the consumer specific legal rights; a consumer may have other rights depending upon where he or she lives. Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion or limitation of special, incidental or consequential damages, or limitations on how long a warranty lasts, so the above exclusion and limitations may not apply to everyone. Outside of the United States, local taxes, tariffs or shipping charges may apply. This warranty does not apply to Callaway Golf® or Odyssey® golf clubs purchased in Australia or New Zealand on or after January 1, 2011. For warranty information for purchases made in Australia and New Zealand on or after that date, see the South Pacific warranty. The above warranty also does not apply to upro gps devices or accessories.
Close
30-Day Money Back Guarantee
Not Satisfied? Return Your Product for a Refund.
Returns/Exchanges For Online Purchases
Callaway Golf wants you to be fully satisfied with every item you purchase. If you are not satisfied with the item you have purchased, you may return it within 30 days of shipment for a full refund of the product price.
If product is unused the refund will credit back to your original payment method.
If product has been used the refund will be in the form of a CallawayGolf.com Gift Card with no expiration date.
In either case a Return Merchandise Authorization (RMA) is required. To obtain your RMA and your FREE UPS Return Shipping Label, please contact a Sales and Customer Service Representative toll free at 1-877-723-5218 or email us.
Credit Card Refunds
On returns, we can only credit the credit card used for the original purchase. Please allow 1-2 billing cycles for the refund credit to appear on your statement.
Gift Card Refunds
On returns, we can only credit the gift card used for the original purchase. Please allow 1-2 billing cycles for the refund credit to appear on your statement.
Close
Your Order Status
Order Status
Order Number
Order Number
Zip Code
Check Status
Reset Your Password
Provide your email address below and we will send you a new password shortly.
Trade-In! Trade-Up!
© 2020 Callaway Golf Company. All rights reserved.
